{
    "id": "1bb62362be054437a96725090c715053",
    "title": "Negative Sentences Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I .................................... like to read science fiction.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do not",
                "has not",
                "not"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0e604c73c5a243659afd3db8eeb54a20"
        },
        {
            "question": "Dogs .................................... chase cats.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not",
                "does not",
                "do not"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "448f1b9de4e0437aa4fdb44ac66b2117"
        },
        {
            "question": "Dogs ................................ like to chase cats.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not",
                "do not",
                "does not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8e19acd726a443deb63212733ae5b83f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Pete ....................................... not want to talk with Ann.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "00091c46d32043cebc8c3a2b91e6ea99"
        },
        {
            "question": "Alice ..................................... not work for an insurance company.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bd6612d766ce40d8b184a72e8d2d30bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................... not like this wine very much.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "56418ccf25b04a70a22ca3142f272a7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ....................................... not enjoy playing with my kids.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ff01bbcecad94edabaab455917763ae2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sharon ...................................... not make models from clay.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7edd4974c55a45349de465251df21975"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ................................. practice the violin every morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does not",
                "have not",
                "do not"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "553475d5d9af469ca7d174e71f9c51c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "My brother ....................................... not earn two hundred dollars a week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9e9b94dcf417468d9110c1e35174aec9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our team ................................. not play well yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "02344feab0214031a3575032998b7ea3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ................................. not go to school by bus.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "has",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "31c7261c5ab04f44ad7e7d81a7670191"
        }
    ]
}